premiumbukkake.com 2017-10-03

# Website Privacy Policy

* * *

## INTRODUCTION

**(A) European Top Project s.r.o.** ("us", "we", or "Company") is committed to respecting the privacy rights of its members of http://premiumbukkake.com (the "Site"). We created the present Website Privacy Policy (the "Privacy Policy") to give you confidence as you visit and use the Site and to demonstrate our commitment to fair information practices and protection of your privacy. The Privacy Policy will explain the information we routinely collect during the operation of the Site and how we utilize it to maximize your experience. 

**(B) The Privacy Policy** is only applicable to the Site, and not to any other websites that you may be able to access from the Site, each of which may have data collection, storage, or use practices and policies that differ materially from this Privacy Policy. Your selection of an ad banner or link may redirect you from the Site to another site controlled by Company or a third party website. Company's other sites may have a privacy policy that is materially different from the Privacy Policy for the Site. Company has no control over and no liability for any third party websites, materials, or for the privacy practices of any such third party website. Please read the privacy policy for any site you visit as third parties may treat your information differently. You should direct any concerns regarding any external link to the third party site's administrator or webmaster.

### 1\. Adults Only Service

The Site contains sexually explicit material and is not intended to be viewed by anyone under the age of 18 or who has not reached the age of majority in their community. The Company will suspend or terminate any accounts which we believe are being used by anyone under the age of eighteen (18) years old or the age of majority in the jurisdiction in which you view the Site; additionally, we reserve the right to report such person to the proper authorities along with all information provided to us by or with respect to such person.

### 2\. Disclosures Made as Necessitated by Law or Safety

All data and/or information ("Information") you provide to the Company are considered confidential. However, all information you provide to us may be shared with other third parties as necessary to comply with applicable law, to cooperate with law enforcement and the court system.

### 3\. Information Collected From You

3.1. During registering as a member we require that you provide certain Information which may include Account Data (i.e., your name, physical address, email address, phone number, username, and password) along with "Demographic Information". Demographic Information may include IP address(es), referring website information, Internet browser used, zip code and/or other data regarding member's location.  
3.2. In order to collect certain information, we utilize small pieces of data that are placed on a member's computer when the member visits the Site ("Cookies"). Some Cookies are stored in a member's web browser and become inactive when the member closes his/her web browser or turns off his/her computer ("Session Cookies"). Other Cookies are longer lasting and reside on a member's hard drive ("Persistent Cookies"). Persistent Cookies remain on a member's computer until the Persistent Cookies expire or are manually deleted. Persistent Cookies may contain email addresses or usernames, but that data is encrypted and can only be interpreted by Company.

### 4\. Using the Information collected

4.1. We inform you that during making payment for access to the Site using third party payment processor you will provide Financial Data (i.e., credit card/billing information) to such payment processor. We do not collect or store any Financial Data, which is collected by our third-party payment processors. Financial Data will only be used by third party processors as necessary to initiate and complete any orders placed by your account.  
4.2. We use Cookies to recognize when member return to the Site, which allows for easier login, customization of member's experience, and overall Site efficiency. We also set Cookies for various tracking and member profiling purposes, such as identifying the pages member visit, the links member click, and the searches member conduct while on the Site. Additionally, we use cookies to optimize the Site, track sales and to facilitate payout agreements with our affiliates when appropriate.  
4.3. In the administration of the Site, we use third party software solutions which also utilize Cookies ("Third Party Cookies"). Through the use of internal methods and the use of Third Party Cookies, we, and our “Partners”, which may include third party service providers, advertisers, advertising networks and platforms, agencies, and other partners may use automated means to collect various types of information about member, member's computer or other device used to access the Site. A representative, non-exhaustive list of the types of information automatically tracked and collected includes the following categories of information when you visit the Site: (a) member's IP address (which allows us to determine member's geographic location); (b) domain servers; (c) type of computer used to access the Site; and (d) type of web browser used to access the Site; and (e) the type of handheld or mobile device used to view the Service (e.g. iOS, Android) (collectively "Traffic Data").  
4.4. Most web browsers allow a user to disable Cookies. While allowing Cookies is not a requirement for membership or use of the Site, if you elect to disable Cookies, some features of the Site features will not function properly as the Site was not designed to operate without Cookies.

### 5\. Member's Responsibility

Credit card transactions are processed through third party processors, which processors only use your information for that purpose. Financial Data is considered private information and will not be shared with us or with third parties except with your authorization and as necessary to carry out orders placed by you with the understanding by you that such transaction(s) may be subject to the rules and policies of such third party. Financial or other Information provided by you to any companies or websites advertising on the Sites or in response to emails sent to you by the Sites are not governed by this Privacy Policy. Any information provided by you to a third party, and any transaction with such a third party, is subject to that third party's terms and conditions and privacy policy.

### 6\. Emails From Us and use of Your Email Address

Member's email address will be used by us to contact member when we have special offers or other information to provide. Such information may include, without limitation, new services offered by us, information relating to member's account and other information related to member's subscription to the Site. We may send member emails prior to and after member has terminated member's membership to our service until such time as member advise us, in accordance with the procedures explained below, that member no longer wish to receive email from us and/or from third parties with whom we have a direct or indirect relationship. We may share member's email address with other third parties, with whom we have a direct or indirect relationship with, for the purposes of sending member special advertisements or promotions. If at any time member no longer wish to receive emails from us or from such third parties member may send us an email at support@premiumbukkake.com. Please note we will never send you an email directly or through our marketing partners without your consent. Please immediately report any emails you may receive, without your prior authorization, that purport to promote the Site.

### 7\. Advertisements

We utilize the services of outside advertising agencies to advertise our services and goods and/or services offered by third parties. Either we or our advertising agencies may use cookies and/or "action tags" to measure advertising effectiveness on an "anonymous basis". Some emails from us may contain advertisements from companies unrelated to the Site. Should member elect to visit any such advertiser's website, we cannot, and do not, make any representations about applicable terms and conditions or privacy policies for such advertisers' websites. If you choose to make any purchases on such sites or accept any offers from such companies, we may provide your information, including Account Data, to the advertiser as necessary to your request. Finally, we cannot, and do not, make any representations about the privacy policies or terms and conditions of advertisements appearing anywhere on our service, whether through our website or emails, this is regardless of whether or not there may be any mentions of or references to any or all of the Site on such advertisers' website(s).

### 8\. Changes to the Website Privacy Policy

We may change the present Website Privacy Policy at any time. Member agreeS that we are under no duty to send the notice of such changes. Instead it is member's responsibility to check this Website Privacy Policy from time to time. No change in the Website Privacy Policy will be effective until thirty (30) days after it is posted, unless the Website Privacy Policy has clear language indicating otherwise.

### 9\. Changes in the Ownership of the Site

The Site are a growing online service. As such, we may have the occasion to buy or sell assets, including but not limited to merger, dissolution, and transfer of ownership. Depending upon the nature of the transaction, we may share any and all Information provided by member to us with third parties, as necessary to initiate, investigate or complete any such transaction(s).
